# **Thomas Wiltshire**

Hello, my name is Thomas. I'm a hard-working, passionate programmer that is currently living in Tongala, Victoria, Australia. Over the last 3 years, I have been studying at the Academy of Interactive Entertainment (AIE) to obtain a Bachelor of Games and Virtual Worlds (Programming).

Location: Sinclair Road Tongala, VIC 3621.

Contacts: +61 466661042 thomas.wiltshire14@icloud.com

Portfolio: thomaswiltshire.com

### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Games and Virtual Worlds**, Academy of Interactive Entertainment — *Melbourne*, *Victoria* 

January 2017 - December 2019

**Primary School / High School,** Kyabram P-12 College / Kyabram St Augustine's College — *Kyabram, Victoria* 

January 2002 - December 2014

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Software Developer Trainee**, Advance Computing — *Kyabram*, *Victoria*

January 2016 - December 2016 (1 Year)

I worked at Advance Computing for around a year where I started a Certificate 3 in Information Technology as a part of my traineeship in software development. I learnt a lot during my time here, had many amazing experiences, obtained a greater knowledge of business and got my first real taste of the software development industry.

## **Crew Member**, Mc Donald's Australia — Echuca, Victoria

March 2015 - January 2016 (1 Year)

I worked at McDonald's within the kitchen environment, being trained in most aspects. During my time here, I gained irreplaceable skills and experience in teamwork, punctuality, leadership, cooking and cleaning.

## **IT Technicians Assistant (Work Placement),** Kyabram Community and Learning Centre — *Kyabram, Victoria*

March 2014 - December 2014 (½ Year)

As a part of my VCAL studies, we were required to find work placement. I worked at KCLC in the IT department, helping with various repair jobs, network issues and general computer assistance.

## NOTABLE PROJECTS (FOUND AT THOMASWILTSHIRE.COM)

Lua C++ Bindings Project, Technical Design Document (Developed for the Gypsy's Tale Project) and Zombie Game (A Passion Project).

#### **EXPERIENCE AND SKILLS**

Languages: C# (3 years), C++ (3 years), Lua (3 years), HTML5/CSS (1 ½ year), Javascript (½ year).

Software: Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, MonoDevelop, SVN, Git, Github, SourceTree.

Hardware: Development Lifecycles of iOS, Android, Windows and Macintosh.

Frameworks: Unity (2 years), Love2D (2 years), WinForms (1 year), UWP (1 year), UE4 (<1/2 year).

Management: Formal education in project management (Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Waterfall), Documentation and UML.

**Other:** Great Teamwork and Troubleshooting Skills.

## **REFERENCES**

AS THIS IS A PUBLIC SITE, REFERENCES ARE AVAILABLE ON REQUEST, TO PROTECT REFERENCE INFORMATION!